Your song, Toxic Till the End, is about a toxic ex of yours.
Is the song about Jaden Smith?
Rosé, do you know why you're here today?
Um, to do the lie detector test.
I'm kind of scared.
This is Judd, our polygraph expert.
Hi.
Are you ready to be hooked up?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm getting in trouble.
Oh, I should have checked these videos out before I came.
Oh, how accurate is it?
It'll be very accurate.
Really?
To begin, I'm going to ask you a few questions to calibrate the machine.
Keep your hands on the table.
Oh, okay.
Is your full name Roseanne Park?
Yes.
Are you a member of Blackpink?
Are you about to take a polygraph exam?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
Judd, are we ready to go?
Good to go.
We're going to start with the category of your life.
My life.
You were born in New Zealand and raised in Australia.
Mm-hmm.
So which country are you more loyal to?
I think most of my memories are from Korea because I've been living there for
the past 12 years.
So I would say Korea.
I'm Korean by blood, so Korea.
Are we still doing the first test singing?
Oh no, we're in it.
Oh, we're in it.
Oh my god, okay.
You're fluent in both English and Korean.
Mm-hmm.
Have you ever slipped into the wrong language while singing?
No, but I've picked up the phone in a different language before.
Mid-sleep.
If you call me mid-sleep, I'll pick up in Korean.
Have you ever forgotten your lyrics on stage?
Yes, many times.
Can you remember them now?
All the lyrics?
All of them.
No, I'm kind of bad.
Have you ever pointed your mic to the crowd because you forgot the lyrics?
Probably.
Probably, yes.
What song was it?
I think it was like Tally or something.
Oh, no.
As if it's your last.
That's always kind of confusing, and I think the girls will agree.
As a kid, you wanted to be an art teacher.
Do you regret giving up on your dreams?
No.
Would you give up fame and fortune to become an art teacher now?
Since you love art, could you draw Judd if we asked you to?
Judd?
Oh, my gosh.
I, ah, maybe.
I'm not very good, actually.
I haven't drawn in a long time.
I could try.
I think I'll, it's hard to draw people because, like, you don't want to make
them feel bad.
Okay, here we go.
Let's try the glasses.
Hmm.
Ah, I'm scared.
I have to do this well.
I don't know if I'm doing well.
The only thing that's accurate here is the glasses.
It's not the worst.
It's good.
Do we approve?
Judd?
Very nice, very nice.
You've said you hated taking piano lessons as a kid.
Considering your career, do you wish you had paid more attention?
Yes, for sure.
I wish I kind of did a few more years of that.
Do you think most kids should give up on their lessons?
No, I don't think they should because I regret it now.
If I'd done it then, then it would be helpful now.
So you don't think you're just better than everyone?
No, no, no.
You spent the last year learning how to drive.
Do you think getting your license at a normal age was too basic?
Yes, very.
I may have just been lazy but That's suspicious Yeah I
was probably just lazy then Never mind Sorry Did you pass the driving test on
the first try?
I failed once.
Yikes.
Have you ever given someone the middle finger while driving?
No.
That's the truth.
Have you ever been recognized on the road by a fan?
No.
Would you ever consider doing something like this to your car?
With my face on it?
Oh my gosh.
No, that looks like a nightmare.
I would hate that.
No, no.
Just tell the truth.
Yes.
Moving on to your career.
You first joined Blackpink in 2016.
Was that the best moment of your life?
Best moment of my life?
Questionable.
I don't know if it was my best moment.
I was very nervous.
Is there an active group chat with you and the rest of Blackpink?
Yes.
Have you ever muted it?
No.
That's the truth.
Who is the most active?
The most active I would say is Jisoo.
Who sends the best memes?
They all send good memes but I think it would be...
Lisa?
Sounds like a question.
Lisa or Jennie.
She's being truthful.
Were there any other names besides Blackpink that were ever considered?
Yes, we used to be almost called Pink Punk.
Was there a name you liked better?
I always liked Blackpink.
Which is the best girl band, Blackpink or this band?
Oh my gosh, that's a hard ques- that's mean!
These girls is fire.
Since I am part of Blackpink, may I say Blackpink?
No, not accurate.
Not accurate?
No, Blackpink is the best!
No, but Spice Girls, they're legendary, so...
Yeah.
Who's your favorite Spice Girl?
Ah, posh.
Tell the truth.
Which is the best girl band, Blackpink or the band from Freaky Friday?
Oh, my gosh.
I love this movie.
But again, I'm going to say Blackpink.
Tell the truth.
Blackpink or this band?
Blackpink.
She's being truthful.
Yes.
But not better than the Spice Girls?
Not that it's my skills.
Apparently.
Your stage name is Rosé.
Do you ever get frustrated by Google searching yourself and just finding wine?
Oh, it kind of started off that way, but lately I've tricked it and it
comes out as me first.
I think I've beat the wine.
Have you ever wished you could change your stage name?
sometimes yeah when people find it hard to pronounce it because it's like rosé i
have but i like it now do you feel like you could never order rosé
at a restaurant yeah i mean i actually don't like rosé wine that's the only
one i don't like so you would never consider selling rosé rosé i know i
would i'd probably make it so i like the taste of it.
Benny Blanco once tweeted, last night I met my idols in reference to meeting you
and Blackpink.
Is Benny Blanco one of your idols?
Idols?
Yes.
That's a lie.
But idol is a big word.
He's a really nice guy.
I love him and he's very talented.
Love you, Benny.
That's truthful.
You also collaborated with his fiance, Selena Gomez on the song Ice Cream.
Mm-hmm.
Did you help set them up?
Oh, no.
Have you ever been a matchmaker for any of your celebrity friends?
For any celebrity friends?
No, I don't remember.
I don't think I have.
Tell the truth.
Yeah.
Has anyone ever set you up?
Yes.
How'd it go?
Great.
Yeah, good.
I'm sweating.
fans say you sing in cursive what do you think singing in cursive means i
don't know i don't try to sing cursive i just try to sing well like
i just want to be good it's like i want people to like my singing
so i'm just trying my best and i think maybe the trying the best part
is why it sounds cursive your album rosie is about the terrible 20s would you
say you are very passionate about the 1920s?
Uh, no.
Do you think you would have been happier living in the 1920s?
No.
Do you think people are generally happier when they reach their 30s?
I think I've heard that it is.
And I think the closer I get to it, I'm starting to enjoy life a
little more.
So I would say yes.
Does it make you nervous that your 30s might just be a continuation of your
terrible 20s?
Oh my God, yeah, that would be terrible.
but I hope not and I don't think it would I mean unless I decide
to just live young and dumb which could be an option but hopefully I enjoy
it more So you don't have an old soul?
I think I have an old soul
Telling truth The song Number One Girl was inspired by toxic comments you read on
social media Do you think social media is always a bad thing?
No
Is that because you appreciate all the fan cams that are made of you?
Yeah, it's nice to have monitoring videos online.
Tell them the truth.
Do you ever look at fan accounts dedicated to you?
Yeah, of course.
What's your favorite account?
Account?
I have a few accounts, and it's always the ones that, like, genuinely are supportive
of me as a person.
Do you have a favorite fan edit of yourself?
Yeah, I do.
What is it?
I feel so narcissistic saying this one.
I do watch back all my Coachella videos.
I'm like, wow, they film me.
They make me look so good.
So that's a good video.
Your single, APT, was produced with Bruno Mars.
You were a fan of Bruno Mars before working with him.
Are you still a fan?
Yes.
I will always be a fan.
If you're such a big fan, what's his best song?
Best song?
Well, my favorite song.
I have a few favorites.
Too Good to Say Goodbye.
I like Chunky Lately.
Locked Out of Heaven is a really fun one to dance to.
You pitched him two other songs.
What were they about?
I pitched, which is really random.
I don't know if this makes any sense, but I pitched Number One Girl and
3AM.
Those were my favorite ones at the time, so I just put them in, but
my main one was ABT.
APT was the one I was bitching.
On October 16th, 2024, Bruno Mars left viral comments on your Instagram post of the
two of you.
Is it true you tried to kiss him?
No.
Not at all.
That's the truth.
So are you calling him a liar?
Yes.
He's a liar.
She's telling the truth.
Bruno Mars is a liar.
You later refer to his comments as fanfic.
Do you think Bruno has read any of Rosé's fanfic?
My fanfic?
I don't know.
I think he may have read his fanfics before.
He nailed it.
Do you ever read fanfic about yourself?
No, I haven't even been into that world before.
It's interesting.
What is a fanfic?
It could be like social media posts, maybe.
Or stories that people make up.
Make up.
Yeah, okay.
So if that's considered fanfic, then yes.
Your song, Toxic Till the End, is about a toxic ex of yours.
Yes, I was inspired a few.
Is the song about Jaden Smith?
No, it's not about Jaden Smith.
He's a good friend, though.
Hi, Jaden.
Miss you lots.
Tell the truth.
Have you ever dated Jaden Smith?
No.
Just tell the truth.
You're famous for your blonde hair.
Have you ever considered changing it to a different color?
I've considered but it always came to a no not yet have you ever forgotten
to bleach your roots forgotten oh yeah I've forgotten and I hated it so now
I don't try not to forget do you think anyone could pull off being blonde
anyone no not anyone I think I think you're selected to
look at being a blonde or a brunette.
What about him, Pete Davidson?
Oh, can I be honest here?
I mean, I have to, actually.
No.
I'm sorry.
He looks better in a different color.
Wicked was one of the biggest films of 2024.
Did you see it?
Not yet.
I've been dying to watch it.
I need some time.
Do you think you would have been a better Glinda than this person?
Oh, not at all.
Never.
Well, I haven't watched it.
She looks great.
And I'm sure she's incredible in it.
Do you think you would have been a better Elphaba than this person?
Oh, no, not at all.
Never.
What?
Could never.
Is that because you don't like the color green?
No.
I think she looks so good.
How do you pull off that color?
Wow.
Green?
Green's not bad.
Have you ever considered starring in a musical?
Starring in a musical?
I've considered before, but I'd have to be good.
What about a revival of a musical, like High School Musical?
High School Musical?
Well, I'm blonde.
I'm going to have to be Sharpay.
Fabulous.
I could do it.
I know all the lyrics to it.
Bigger and better than that.
Need a little fabulous to get me getting along.
Be a little fabulous, is that so wrong?
Oh, sorry.
I've lost my voice.
I've been having too much fun.
You mentioned you were inspired by this woman.
Yes.
This is one of the movies that really made me want to be a singer.
Would you want to play Satine in a remake of Moulin Rouge?
My gosh.
That would be too good to be true.
I would absolutely love to do that.
So you think you're a better singer than Nicole Kidman?
No
Just tell the truth No, she was so good, yeah Would you ever okay a
biopic about your life?
What is that?
A film about you About me?
Would I ever like it?
If I have done great things, then maybe Who would you want to play you?
Oh, that's such a good question Somebody Asian with blonde hair
That speaks Korean and English and can pull off an Australian accent.
Final question.
At any point did you lie during this interview and we didn't catch you?
No, I don't think I lied.
I'm not a very good liar.
You could like towel on my face.
So I probably don't even need this.
She's being truthful.